

VARSHA GHUGARE PIPING DESIGNER

Profile

[Enter bio here]

Mrs varsha Ghugare is Piping Designer with 10+year Experience. Her diversified experience include Preparing 3D model for Equipment & piping in Revit & sp3d. she has been with Jacobs for last 3 Years.

This experience provides me a crucial knowledge about utility & piping services and helps me to stepping ahead in an organization for becoming an effective

employee. The software skill and technical knowledge can apply my implementation and support experience along with my strong analytical, creative and inter-personal skills in order to gain tangible and intangible benefits for the organizatio

Key skills | Areas of expertise

Piping & Equipment model on Revit. Preparing and Reviewing the Piping & with all MEP services and Reviewing the 3D model using Navisworks.
Coordination with other discipline and Internal Project groups for various activities.

Education | Qualifications

 Passed B.sc Exam in the year Mar 2009Completed 'Piping design & Draughtman" course in the year Jan 2011.

Registrations | Certifications

Nil

Memberships | Affiliations

Nil

Training

• Revit staff training in Previous company

Awards | Honors

Nil

Languages

• English, Marathi ,Hindi

Employment history

- OCT 2019 to present, Jacobs Limited.
- Jan 2013 To Feb 2019 ,GMP Technical Solution PVT. LTD.
- 5th March 2012 To Jan 2013 ,PROGRESSIVE ENGINNERING WORKS.
- Jan 2011 To March 2012, Mott-Macdonalds.

Relevant project experience

Include all relevant experience (not just Jacobs), in reverse chronological order. Repeat this format as needed. Remember to delete this instructional text.

GIGA FACTORY BERLIN, GERMANY, CONFIDENTIAL

Project BOB: Giga Factory Berlin, Germany, Confidential

Role: Piping Designer

Responsibilities: 3D Revit Modelling of Process pipng. Clash detection with other services in Navisworks, Checking for Pipe supports as per revised drawings. Preparing BOQ from the 3D Model, PDF of sheets and publishing in BIM 360.

NSBS, DELTA OHIOs

Client: NSBSL Role: Piping Responsibilities: Piping modeling, Piping supporting, Review all internal design check documents from all disciplines, Co-ordination & other activities.

BUCKEYE PHASE-3 (SIDNEY)

Client: [Client name]

Role: PIPING DESIGNER-Sp3D

Responsibilities: Piping modeling, Equipment modeling, Review all internal design check documents from all disciplines, Co-ordination & other activities.

Reference/s

GMP TECHNICAL SOLUTIONS PVT LTD.

Piping Designer Executive- Autocad-2014, Revit-2013

IMI (NIGERIA)

Jan 2013 To Feb 2019

Title: : PIPING DESIGNER- CAD & REVIT

Responsibilities: Initial designing of piping layout; Preparation bill of Quantity for tendering purpose, Preparation of P&ID, Preparation of piping layout, fire water hydrant layout, extraction of bill of material, structure BOQ & structure weight calculation, 3D drawing on MEP Revit software.

KPMA (ALGERIA)

Title:: PIPING DESIGNER-CAD

Responsibilities: Initial designing of piping layout; Preparation bill of Quantity for tendering purpose, Preparation of P&ID, Preparation of piping layout, fire water hydrant layout, extraction of bill of material.

BAHRAIN PHARMA (BAHRAIN)

Title: : PIPING DESIGNER- CAD

Responsibilities: Initial designing of piping layout; Preparation bill of Quantity for tendering purpose, Preparation of P&ID, Preparation of piping layout, fire water hydrant layout, extraction of bill of material, 3D drawing on MEP Revit software.

STRIDE (SUDAN)

Title:: PIPING DESIGNER-CAD

Responsibilities: Initial designing of piping layout; Preparation bill of Quantity for tendering purpose, Preparation of P&ID, Preparation of piping layout, fire water hydrant layout, extraction of bill of material.

PROGRESSIVE ENGINEERING WORKS

Piping Designer- Design & Drafting on autocad

HPCL PROJRCT (LONI)

Title:: PIPING DESIGNER

Responsibilities: Isometrics from GAD. Etraction of Bill of Material.

HPCL NEW POL DEPOT PROJRCT (KADAPA)

[Document number] 2

Title:: PIPING DESIGNER

Responsibilities: Isometrics from GAD. Etraction of Bill of Material

VOLTAS PROJECT AT KOCHI & TRIVENDRUM

Title:: PIPING DESIGNER

Responsibilities: Preparation BOQ from GAD, Preparation Sectional view from GAD, Isometrics

from GAD. Etraction of Bill of Material

"Mott-Macdonalds"

Cad operato

As built project of Yibal & musallam

Title: Cad operator

Responsibilities: As built work.

[Document number] 3